CALAB LABARDA: Oh, hi.
My name is Calab Labarda, I'm a third degree black belt in Taekwondo.
Alright, so now, I'm going to be showing you different types of nunchucks, okay.
This pair right here that I have with me, are hard, Bruce Lee styled nunchucks, okay.
Like I said before, these right here, these little, fancy, shiny pins in 'em, they're just for looks and--to make them look fancy and shiny when you spin it around, to give it some flair, okay.
It has a chain with it, okay.
If ever you used the chain nunchuck, make sure it's the length of your hand, okay.
That's how you pick out a good nunchuck.
Okay, you could see right here, that two links have been removed.
You can use it, just cut those off with a saw, okay.
Also, these ones are more hardcore, okay.
You want to be pretty good with nunchucks before you even move on to these ones, 'cause they will knock you out, alright.
So, when you're first starting out, you want to go ahead and use some soft, full nunchucks like these ones, okay.
Now, the difference between that and your regular nunchuck, okay, look at the string length, okay.
These are going to be a lot faster and a lot quicker.
These are going to be little bit slower but it delivers more of a "umph", okay.
This is more of the whip, okay.
They're still both realistic.
They can use for fighting and they're both very strong.
But this one will deliver a fast whip, okay.
They're delivered for fast strikes very quickly, okay.
Now, the kind I'm going to be using today are the full length professional nunchucks, okay.
You can just order these online, or wherever you find them.
I'd like to test my nunchucks out before I use them, and this is the best pair that I found.
They're weighted, there's pins in them, and you can see, this is where you hold them, they're weighted, okay.
The string is one, one-inch long, okay.
And you can see the stick, this is maple wood.
It's very strong nunchuck.
It's very realistic.
It's the real thing.
I can put it on my back pocket and use it as a weapon.